<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rce on zero.lol</title>
    <link>/tags/rce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rce on zero.lol</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/rce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hey Gucci, you Gucci?</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-05-09-hey-gucci-you-gucci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-05-09-hey-gucci-you-gucci/</guid>
      <description>0x01 Introduction Around March 14th 2019 I found Local File Inclusion, Path Traversal and File Write on the Gucci subdomain glft.gucci.com on port 3443 (https://glft.gucci.com:3443/). When attempting to go to the subdomain on the regular port 80/433 you would be met with a message that the subdomain was an intranet interface. So all of the findings combined, a malicious actor could have read local files, uploaded a phishing page, upload a shell which could have led to a reverse shell, opening up a potential of traversing the internal network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun With Custom URI Schemes</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-22-fun-with-uri-handlers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-22-fun-with-uri-handlers/</guid>
      <description>0x01 Introduction Over the past month or so, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent quite a bit of time reading and experimenting with custom URI schemes. As the last post on this blog clearly demonstrated, a poorly implemented custom URI can have a number of security concerns. When I say &amp;ldquo;a number&amp;rdquo;, it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m about to bring a few more to light, using EA&amp;rsquo;s Origin Client as our crash test dummy.
TL;DR: Another Origin RCE, unrelated to CVE-2019-11354.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Questionable Journey From XSS to RCE</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-05-13-xss-to-rce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-05-13-xss-to-rce/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As many of you reading this probably already know, in mid April, a good friend of mine (@Daley) and I located a Remote Code Execution vulnerability in EA&amp;rsquo;s Origin client (CVE-2019-11354). Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to go in depth on how we discovered this vulnerability, along with a couple others we needed to chain along the way ;pp

Debugging Origin A lot of what was discovered was enabled by QtWebEngine debugging.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>